David C. Mahoney Company Records
Hartford History Center, Hartford Public Library
- Items
  - 15-21 Willow Street, 1962; Block #4, Parcel 3. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan and two photographs of a frame two-family dwelling and a brick six-family dwelling. (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - 16-20 Willow Street, 1962; Block #3, Parcel 12. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan and one photograph of a frame four-family dwelling. (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - 30 Willow Street, 1962; Block #3, Parcel 9. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan and one photograph of a frame single family house. (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - 34-36 Willow Street, 1962; Block #2, Parcel 8. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan and one photograph of brick three-family house. (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - 35 Willow Street, 1962; Block #4, Parcel 5. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan and one photograph of Hartford Mill Supply Co. (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - 40 Willow Street, 1962; Block #3, Parcel 7. Typescript real estate appraisal and site plan showing a house and garage with one photograph of the house. (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - 44-46 Willow Street, 1962; Block #3, Parcel 6. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan and one photograph of a brick three-family dwelling. (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - 55 Willow Street, 1962; Block #4, Parcel 6. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan and one photograph of a vacant lot used as a parking lot. (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Willow Street, south side, 1962; Block #4, Parcel 4. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan and one photograph of a tree beside the Park River. (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - 27-33 Woodbine Street, 1962; Block #2, Parcel 17. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan and two photographs of a frame two-family house and a brick tenement, office, and warehouse building. (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - 37 Woodbine Street, 1962; Block #2, Parcel 16. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan showing with two photographs of a frame single-family house and garage. (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - 41 Woodbine Street, 1962; Block #2, Parcel 13. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan and one photograph of a frame single family dwelling. (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - 45-47 Woodbine Street, 1962; Block #2, Parcel 12. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan showing with two photographs of a frame three-family house and garage. (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - 51-53 Woodbine Street, 1962; Block #2, Parcel 9. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan with two photographs of a frame two-family house and a frame single-family house. (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - 55-57 Woodbine Street, 1962; Block #2, Parcel 8. Typescript real estate appraisal and site plan of a two-family dwelling with one photograph showing automobiles parked on the property. (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - 81-89 Woodbine Street, 1962; Block #2, Parcel 2. Typescript description, three site plans, and one photograph of a brick building, apparently a combination warehouse and office. (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Woodbine Street, west side, 1962?; Block #2, Parcel 1. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan with one photograph of the property, a vacant lot used as a parking lot. (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - 23-25 Woodbridge Street, 1962?; Block #4, Parcel 24. Brief typescript description, site plan and one photograph of a brick six-family dwelling. (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - 24-26 Woodbridge Street, 1962?; Block #3, Parcel 13. Brief typescript description, site plan and one negative and photograph of an office, storage and tenement building. (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - 23 Woodbridge Street, 1962?; Block #3, Parcel 12. Brief typescript description, site plan and one negative and photograph of three-family dwelling. (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - 29 Woodbridge Street, 1962?; Block #4, Parcel 21. Brief typescript description, site plan and two negatives and photographs of a three-family dwelling and store housing the Woodbridge Package Store and a four-car garage. (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - 30 Woodbridge Street, 1962?; Block #3, Parcel 11. Brief typescript description, site plan and three negatives and photographs showing a brick three-family dwelling and a one-car garage. (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - 31-33 Woodbridge Street, 1962?; Block #4, Parcel 20. Brief typescript description, site plan and one negative and photograph of a brick multiple-family dwelling. (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - 32-34 Woodbridge Street, 1962?; Block #3, Parcel 10. Brief typescript description, site plan and one negative and photograph of a brick four-family dwelling. (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - 35-37 Woodbridge Street, 1962?; Block #4, Parcel? Brief typescript description, site plan and three negatives and photographs showing a brick six-family dwelling and an adjoining two-family dwelling. (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - 36-38 Woodbridge Street, 1962?; Block #3, Parcel 9. Brief typescript description, site plan and one negative and photograph of a brick six-family dwelling. (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - 39-41 Woodbridge Street, 1962?; Block #4, Parcel 16. Brief typescript description, site plan and three negatives and photographs of two adjacent brick three-family dwellings and a garage. (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - 40 Woodbridge Street, 1962?; Block #3, Parcel 6. Brief typescript description, site plan and one negative and photograph of a store and tenement building in dilapidated condition. (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - 42 Woodbridge Street, 1962?; Block #3, Parcel 5. Brief typescript description, site plan and one negative and photograph of a brick six-family dwelling. (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - 42 Woodbridge Street, 1962?; Block #4, Parcel 13. Brief typescript description, site plan and one negative and photograph of a brick three-family dwelling. (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - 44-46 Woodbridge Street, 1962?; Block #3, Parcel 4. Brief typescript description, site plan and one negative and photograph of a brick office and tenement building. (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - 45-47 Woodbridge Street, 1962?; Block #4, Parcel 12. Brief typescript description, site plan and one negative and photograph of a brick six-family dwelling. (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - 48-50 Woodbridge Street, 1962?; Block #3, Parcel 3. Brief typescript description, site plan and three negatives and photographs showing three vacant, dilapidated buildings, two multiple-family dwellings and a former bakery. (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - 49-51 Woodbridge Street, 1962?; Block #4, Parcel 9. Brief typescript description, site plan and one negative and photograph of a brick six-family dwelling. (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - 52-54 Woodbridge Street, 1962?; Block #3, Parcel 2. Site plan and typescript description of a store and tenement building and a four-car garage. (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Unidentified maps and photographs, Includes a print of Heublein Tower and a photograph of a brick commercial with signs that read "Irvin" and "Keyboard." (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Map of Ann Street, Asylum Street, Church Street, Chapel Street, Haynes Street, Pearl Street, Pratt Street, n.d.; Map prepared by the Department of Engineering. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Bushnell Plaza Project, 1961; Property Map issued by the Hartford Redevelopment Agency showing private property to be acquired. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Map of the City of Hartford, 1959; Map prepared by the Department of Engineering. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - James L. Goodwin estate, 1922; "Taken from Spencer and Washburn map." (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Sheldon-Charter Oak Avenue, n.d.; Map prepared by the Department of Engineering, showing buildings on Main Street, South Prospect Street, Governor Street, Sheldon Street, Charter Oak Avenue. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Sheldon-Charter Oak neighborhood, n.d.; Map prepared by the Department of Engineering, showing area between the Connecticut River and Whitehead Highway and Wyllys Street and Van Block Avenue. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Sheldon-Charter Oak Project (Section A), 1964; Map drawn by John D. Boyd for the Hartford Redevelopment Agency with a key to property owners. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Sheldon-Charter Oak Project (Section A), 1964; Map drawn by John D. Boyd for the Hartford Redevelopment Agency with a key to property owners. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Trumbull Street Project, Property Map No. 1, 1963; Map drawn by S. J. Buccleri for the Hartford Redevelopment Agency with a key to property owners. 2 copies with variations. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Trumbull Street Project, Property Map No. 1, 1964; Map drawn by S. J. Buccleri for the Hartford Redevelopment Agency with a key to property owners, showing parcels to be appraised. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Trumbull Street Project, Property Map No. 2, 1963-1964; Map drawn by S. J. Buccleri for the Hartford Redevelopment Agency with a key to property owners. 2 copies with variations. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Underwood Project, 1962?; Map drawn for the Hartford Redevelopment Agency. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Underwood Project, 1962; Map drawn by S. J. Buccleri for the Hartford Redevelopment Agency with a key to property owners. 2 copies, one showing property values. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Underwood Project vicinity, 1962?; Map drawn by J.D.B. for the Hartford Redevelopment Agency showing area subject to flooding and highway under construction (I-84). (Box 5, Folder 14)